(Leonard:)I don't get how she can just announce...
...that an old boyfriend is gonna sleep
on her couch.
(Sheldon:)Hey, I thought of a game
we can play in the car.
I don't wanna play a game, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)It's called Scientists.
Now, I will name three scientists...
...you'll put them in order of the size
of their contribution to their fields.
(Sheldon:)To make this game
even more compelling...
(Sheldon:)...you must consider only the
contribution of the man to the field...
(Sheldon:)...not the validity of the field itself.
(Sheldon:)For example,
Abu Musa Jabir ibn Hayyan...
(Sheldon:)...made a greater contribution
to the discredited field of alchemy...
(Sheldon:)...than Halbert Vanderplatt
made to neurobiology.
(Sheldon:)Okay. Ready to have some fun?
(Leonard:)An old boyfriend
who's "definitely not gay."
You know, that's what a guy
likes to hear. "Definitely."
(Sheldon:)All right, I'll start with an easy one.
(Sheldon:)Um, Isaac Newton, Madame Curie
and Niels Bohr.
(Leonard:)And then I say one little thing
and I end up being the bad guy.
(Sheldon:)Hint. Madame Curie had her husband
to help her.
(Leonard:)What am I supposed to say?
"Sure, Penny. I'm cool with your old
boyfriend sleeping in your apartment."